Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers YCAL MSS 722
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 344633; 100.63 Linear Feet (117 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  - Oversize Material, circa 1916-1998; 344654
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1987-1989; 344662; 4 Folders (Box 163 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Newspapers (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1989-1992; 344661; 3 Folders (Box 164 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Family photographs (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1920s-1960s; 344660 (Box 165 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Personal photographs (from Personal and Other Papers), 344659; 6 Folders (Box 165 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Kramer, Larry by Annie Leibovitz (from Personal and Other Papers), 344658 (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Personal photographs (from Personal and Other Papers), 344657 (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, Women in Love (from Personal and Other Papers), 344656; 3 Folders (Box 166 (Oversize))
    - Framed print of the poem "Bore," inscribed "Love, Charlie" (from Personal and Other Papers), 344655 (Box 167 (Oversize))
  - Rolled Storage, 344645
    - Family Papers, Certificates, Arthur Kramer / 1916 Class Reunion photograph, George Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1950s-1960s; 344653 (Box 168 (Oversize))
    - Family Papers, Certificates, Rea Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 1920s-1930s; 344652 (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers), 344651 (Box 170 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers), 344650 (Box 171 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers), 344649 (Box 172 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers), 344648 (Box 173 (Oversize))
    - Printed Material, Rolled posters, unsorted (from Personal and Other Papers), 344647 (Box 174 (Roll))
    - Wall Mural by Larry Kramer (from Personal and Other Papers), 344646 (Box 175 (Roll))
  - Broadsides, 344642
    - Printed Material, The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, poster (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 2000; 344644 (Box 176 (Broadside))
    - Printed Material, The Tragedy of Today's Gays, poster (from Personal and Other Papers), circa 2005; 344643 (Box 177(Broadside))
  - Computer media, 344637
    Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - PowerBook laptop, 344638
      Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information: Disk #2008.ycal..22518.211.
      General
      Beinecke has removed and retained the internal hard drive from the PowerBook G4 laptop computer originally included in this collection. The rest of the machine has been deaccessioned.
      - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0237; 1 Internal Hard Drives; 30005821440 bytes 30 Gigabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 181)
    - External hard drive, prior to 2008; 39002102357135 (Box 181, Box 264)
      Older model external hard drive, brand unknown. The external hard drive case has been kept for artifactual value and is stored in Box 264; the internal drive has been removed, the content captured, and the drive stored in Box 181.
    - CN EH, 2008-ycal-22518-0215; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - LETTRIX Software Version 3.6, 2008-ycal-22518-0216; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - LETTRIX Software Version 3.6, 2008-ycal-22518-0217; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - disk optimizer, 2008-ycal-22518-0218; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0219; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Program Disk Disk 1 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0220; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Microsoft Spell Disk 2 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0221; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Thesaurus Disk 3 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0222; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Utilities/Setup Disk Disk 4 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0223; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Printer Disk 1 Disk 5 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0224; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Printer Disk 2 Disk 6 of 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0225; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Learning Microsoft Word Essentials for Keyboard and Mouse Disk 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0226; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Learning Microsoft Word Advanced Lessons for Keyboard Disk 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0227; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Microsoft Word Learning Microsoft Word Advanced Lessons for Mouse Disk 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0228; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - PROCOMM 2.4.2 PROGRAM, 2008-ycal-22518-0229; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - PROCOMM 2.4.2 DOCUMENTATION, 2008-ycal-22518-0230; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - BACKUP OF PCANYWHERE, 2008-ycal-22518-0231; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - FASTBACK UNP, 2008-ycal-22518-0232; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - LIGHTNING Version 4.2, 2008-ycal-22518-0233; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - REMOTE 1.3 ENTER-> A:INSTALL, 2008-ycal-22518-0234; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - SCRIPTOR System: Compaq 286 Disk: Program Format: DOS Version: 2.9d Configured for: Larry Kramer, 2008-ycal-22518-0235; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - Lotus Magellan Auto-Demo, 2008-ycal-22518-0236; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 180)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0001; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0002; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0003; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Earliest History I, 2008-ycal-22518-0004; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - TAP Part one, 2008-ycal-22518-0005; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - TNH SP FD, 2008-ycal-22518-0006; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0007; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - SUITCASE II, 2008-ycal-22518-0008; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0009; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0010; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - 21 BV 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0011; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0012; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - FV/RFTH, 2008-ycal-22518-0013; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0014; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - 19 Bv 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0015; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - 20 BV 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0016; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Just Say NO Rehearsal Shots 3/07 Theatre of NOTE, 2008-ycal-22518-0017; 1 CD-Rs (Box 178)
    - Larry Kramer a few pix for friends RUHE ©, 2008-ycal-22518-0018; 1 CD-Rs (Box 178)
    - Charlie Rose 7/19/05 Larry Kramer, 2008-ycal-22518-0019; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 178)
    - Charlie Rose 7/19/05 Larry Kramer, 2008-ycal-22518-0020; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 178)
    - Larry Kramer Speech at the LGBT Center New York March 13, 2007, 2008-ycal-22518-0021; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 178)
    - TAP 1+2 - less some formatting, 2008-ycal-22518-0022; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0023; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - TAP - FD Findit TNH S/P, 2008-ycal-22518-0024; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - TAP 6/4/98, 2008-ycal-22518-0025; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - FONTS, 2008-ycal-22518-0026; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0027; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - G3., 2008-ycal-22518-0028; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0029; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - Power Book Install, 2008-ycal-22518-0030; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0031; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - WORD DOC, 2008-ycal-22518-0032; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - Add. Software, 2008-ycal-22518-0033; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0034; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - A, 2008-ycal-22518-0035; 1 ZIP Disks (Box 178)
    - GLYPHIX PROPORTIONAL FONTS ENTER "A:INSTALL", 2008-ycal-22518-0036; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - WordPerfect 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0037; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - WordPerfect 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0038; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Speller, 2008-ycal-22518-0039; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Thesaurus, 2008-ycal-22518-0040a; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Fonts/Graphics, 2008-ycal-22518-0040b; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - PTR Program, 2008-ycal-22518-0041; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Printer 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0042; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Printer 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0043; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Printer 3, 2008-ycal-22518-0044; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Printer 4, 2008-ycal-22518-0045; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Learning, 2008-ycal-22518-0046; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Conversion, 2008-ycal-22518-0047; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - WordPerfect/HP LaserJet Series II Print Sample Demo Diskette #1, 2008-ycal-22518-0048; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - WordPerfect/HP LaserJet Series II Print Sample Demo Diskette #2, 2008-ycal-22518-0049; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - fh8/9, 2008-ycal-22518-0050; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - RubinI, 2008-ycal-22518-0051; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - 5nh 6nh 7nh 8nh 9nh 4/20 9aNH, 2008-ycal-22518-0052; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - SAF BU COLE BILLY BBC2 9bnh 10nh, 2008-ycal-22518-0053; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - IINA IINH, 2008-ycal-22518-0054; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - JUST SAY NO JSNT=TITLE JSNCC JSNCC Cast etc JSN10=ACT I ACT3=ACT II MS WORD 4, 2008-ycal-22518-0055; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - Play6 jpy jSN6/7/8, 2008-ycal-22518-0056; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - JUST SAY NO Force, 2008-ycal-22518-0057; 1 5.25_floppy_disks (Box 178)
    - NISUS 3.05 - > 3.06 UPDATE DISK, 2008-ycal-22518-0058; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - SUITCASE, 2008-ycal-22518-0059; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - PARAGON concepts, inc., 2008-ycal-22518-0060; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Utilities Disk Adobe Type Library, 2008-ycal-22518-0061; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word 4. 00B, 2008-ycal-22518-0062; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word 4. 00B, 2008-ycal-22518-0063; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word 4.00B., 2008-ycal-22518-0064; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Utilities 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0065; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Utilities 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0066; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Program, 2008-ycal-22518-0067; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MacEnvelope, 2008-ycal-22518-0068; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - EDUCORP MACWORLD, 2008-ycal-22518-0069; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Canard Press, 2008-ycal-22518-0070; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 1.33 SCRIPTWRITER AI Help Disk, 2008-ycal-22518-0071; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 6.03 SCRIPTWRITER AI System Disk, 2008-ycal-22518-0072; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Quicken, 2008-ycal-22518-0073; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - AutoSave II, 2008-ycal-22518-0074; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - DISKWORLD SAMPLER 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0075; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WORDPERFECT FOR THE MACINTOSH Installer old, 2008-ycal-22518-0076; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 2.0 Part 2 old, 2008-ycal-22518-0077; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect Help/Learn old, 2008-ycal-22518-0078; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Dictionary/Thesaurus old, 2008-ycal-22518-0079; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Word Perfect 2.0 Part 1 old, 2008-ycal-22518-0080; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - VIRUS STUFF, 2008-ycal-22518-0081; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - SCRIPTOR for Macintosh Computers Program Disk Configured for: Larry Kramer Ver: 1.5 Screenplay Formatting Software, 2008-ycal-22518-0082; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - SCRIPTOR…for the Professional Screenwriter Version 1.5b8 Configured for: Larry Kramer, 2008-ycal-22518-0083; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WORDPERFECT FOR THE MACINTOSH Installer, 2008-ycal-22518-0084; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MACINTOSH WordPerfect 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0085; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0086; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 3, 2008-ycal-22518-0087; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 4, 2008-ycal-22518-0088; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WORDPERFECT FOR THE MACINTOSH Installer 009087, 2008-ycal-22518-0089; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0090; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0091; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 3, 2008-ycal-22518-0092; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 4, 2008-ycal-22518-0093; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - UTOPIA GROKWARE PRESENTS Flowfazer V1.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0094; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - COLORIZED Version 1.14, 2008-ycal-22518-0095; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - COLORIZED Version 1.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0096; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MACINTOSH UTILITIES PC TOOLS Deluxe, 2008-ycal-22518-0097; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - FASTCACHE || 64K static RAM cache for the Macintosh IIci, 2008-ycal-22518-0098; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - CIVILIZED SOFTWARE from Eastgate Systems, Inc. Fontina, 2008-ycal-22518-0099; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MasterStrokes Keyboard Enhancement Software for the MAC, 2008-ycal-22518-0100; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BMUG Disk Business 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0101; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MacUser STACK MAGIC, 2008-ycal-22518-0102; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Adobe TypeManager Version 1.2 Upgrade, 2008-ycal-22518-0103; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Adobe TypeManager, 2008-ycal-22518-0104; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Larry Kramer Screen Fonts Adobe Helvetica Condensed Helvetica Black Helvetica Light Bodoni Reg. Bodoni Poster, 2008-ycal-22518-0105; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Program Disk 2.12 Updater QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0106; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Data Disk 2.11 Upgrade QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0107; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Program Disk 2.11 Upgrade Installer QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0108; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Sample Disk QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0109; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Data Disk QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0110; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Program Disk QuarkXPress, 2008-ycal-22518-0111; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - A Heart Hurt Beyond Healing (WP), 2008-ycal-22518-0112; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - FH Drafts: 8 9 10, 2008-ycal-22518-0113; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - FH backups, 2008-ycal-22518-0114; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Search For My Heart No Longer The Redfern Document Glossdalia[?] HA Outline, 2008-ycal-22518-0115; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WRITINGS - MISC.2, 2008-ycal-22518-0116; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - INITS, 2008-ycal-22518-0117; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Aachen Font, 2008-ycal-22518-0118; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Furniture of Home 7th draft, 2008-ycal-22518-0119; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Letters (2), 2008-ycal-22518-0120; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WRITINGS MISC - 1 Letters (1), 2008-ycal-22518-0121; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MASTURBOV GDNS Masturbov Gardens Scenes for Tomorrow Lives on Hred, 2008-ycal-22518-0122; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Larry! Quark: reports external HA Breeders| PC Backup dera(?), 2008-ycal-22518-0123; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Larry's database Filemaker, 2008-ycal-22518-0124; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - TAP Breeders 2 HA Section one HA Revision one TAP notes, 2008-ycal-22518-0125; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - LARRY'S TETRIS 5 - ROTATE 2- DROP 4 - LEFT 6 - RIGHT, 2008-ycal-22518-0126; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - CLICK CHANGE, 2008-ycal-22518-0127; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - QUICK & AMAZING An Intro. to QuicKeys 2, QuickMail, & Amazing Paint, 2008-ycal-22518-0128; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - ASHTON-TATE FullWrite Professional Dictionary and File Disk, 2008-ycal-22518-0129; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - ASHTON-TATE FullWrite Professional Macintosh SYSTEM Disk, 2008-ycal-22518-0130; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - ASHTON-TATE FullWrite Professional APPLICATION DISK EVALUATION COPY, 2008-ycal-22518-0131; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - HyperCard Program, 2008-ycal-22518-0132; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MACINTOSH Printing Tools 6.05, 2008-ycal-22518-0133; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MACINTOSH System Tools 6.05, 2008-ycal-22518-0134; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 6.05 MACINTOSH Utilities 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0135; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - SYS 6.0.5 Macintosh Utilities Disk 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0136; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh LaserWriter IINT/NTX Fonts, 2008-ycal-22518-0137; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh LaserWriter II Installation Disk, 2008-ycal-22518-0138; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh HyperCard and Stacks, 2008-ycal-22518-0139; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh Your Apple Tour of the Macintosh IIcx Computer, 2008-ycal-22518-0140; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh HyperCard Help, 2008-ycal-22518-0141; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh HyperCard Ideas, 2008-ycal-22518-0142; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh Macintosh Printing Tools, 2008-ycal-22518-0143; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh Macintosh Utilities Disk 1, 2008-ycal-22518-0144; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh Macintosh System Tools, 2008-ycal-22518-0145; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Macintosh Macintosh Utilities Disk 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0146; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - LATEST VERSION, 2008-ycal-22518-0147; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - LOGITECH MouseKey Software, 2008-ycal-22518-0148; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - QUICKEYS2 CESOFTWARE 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0149; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - EXTRAS QUICKEYS2 CESOFTWARE 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0150; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - QUICKEYS2 CESOFTWARE, 2008-ycal-22518-0151; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - EXTRAS QUICKEYS2 CESOFTWARE, 2008-ycal-22518-0152; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MasterJuggler ALSoft, 2008-ycal-22518-0153; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MasterJuggler ALSoft, 2008-ycal-22518-0154; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - on cue the ultimate file launcher, 2008-ycal-22518-0155; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - QuickDEX, 2008-ycal-22518-0156; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 107 NYMUG New York Macusers' Group, Inc., 2008-ycal-22518-0157; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 1.33 SCRIPTWRITER AI American Intelliware for Apple Macintosh, 2008-ycal-22518-0158; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor V 3.01, 2008-ycal-22518-0159; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor Other Files, 2008-ycal-22518-0160; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor Dictionary & Thesaurus, 2008-ycal-22518-0161; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - SCRIPTWRITER AI American Intelliware for Apple Macintosh Demonstration, 2008-ycal-22518-0162; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BACKMATIC V. 2.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0163; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BACKMATIC V. 2.01, 2008-ycal-22518-0164; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor DEMO, 2008-ycal-22518-0165; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor Dictionary & Thesaurus, 2008-ycal-22518-0166; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - NISUS The Amazing Word Processor, 2008-ycal-22518-0167; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 1 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0168; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 2 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0169; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 3 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0170; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 4 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0171; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WordPerfect 5 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0172; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU 7 Oct 89 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0173; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU 7 Oct 89 3, 2008-ycal-22518-0174; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU 7 Oct 89 5, 2008-ycal-22518-0175; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU. DIR? 7 Oct 89 6, 2008-ycal-22518-0176; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU 11 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0177; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MDA Rev 12 BU 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0178; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 13 BU 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0179; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 14 BU 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0180; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 15 BU 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0181; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU 7 Oct 89 17, 2008-ycal-22518-0182; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 18 BU 7 Oct 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0183; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 22 BU 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0184; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 23 BU 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0185; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 24 BU 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0186; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 25 BU 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0187; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - 26 BU 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0188; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - BU DIRECTORY (27) 7 OCT 89, 2008-ycal-22518-0189; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - CPU CONNECTIX POWERBOOK UTILITIES Version 2.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0190; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - GRAMMER AND SPELLING PLUG-IN MODULE UPDATE WORD FOR MACINTOSH, 2008-ycal-22518-0191; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - DEFAULT FONT PATCH FOR WORD 5.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0192; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Install Apple Macintosh Series Version 5.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0193; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Converters Apple Macintosh Series, 2008-ycal-22518-0194; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Program Apple Macintosh Series, 2008-ycal-22518-0195; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Commands Apple Macintosh Series, 2008-ycal-22518-0196; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Microsoft Word Proofing Tools Apple Macintosh Series, 2008-ycal-22518-0197; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Adobe Type Manager v. 2.0, 2008-ycal-22518-0198; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - A ZILLION KAJILLION RHYMES, 2008-ycal-22518-0199; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Adobe Type Reunion, 2008-ycal-22518-0200; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Utilities Disk Adobe Type Library, 2008-ycal-22518-0201; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MacinStor Installer Version 3.0.1 DISK 1 of 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0202; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - MacinStor Installer Version 3.0.1 DISK 2 of 2, 2008-ycal-22518-0203; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Novel, 2008-ycal-22518-0204; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Novel Washington, 2008-ycal-22518-0205; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Master Juggler Copy 7.0. Computer, 2008-ycal-22518-0206; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Utilities Disk SAM JR MACROMANAGER Automac 3, 2008-ycal-22518-0207; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - E-MACHINES Accessories Disk Macintosh II, 2008-ycal-22518-0208; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - TAP PART II, 2008-ycal-22518-0209; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - The American People (Master) PI I 13 Nov 91, 2008-ycal-22518-0210; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - PowerBook THE DIGITAL NOMAD'S GUIDE, 2008-ycal-22518-0211; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)